(Leonard:)Is that why they sent you
to boarding school?
(Sheldon:)No. That was the result
of my work with lasers.
[LILY ALLEN'S "SMILE" PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
I go ahead and smile
New neighbor?
SHELDON:
Evidently.
(Leonard:)Significant improvement
over the old neighbor.
Two-hundred pound transvestite
with a skin condition? Yes, she is.
(Penny:)Oh, hi.
(Sheldon:)- Hi.
- Hi.
(Penny:)Hi?
(Leonard:)We don't mean to interrupt.
We live across the hall.
(Penny:)Oh, that's nice.
No. We don't live together. I mean...
(Leonard:)...we live together, but in separate,
heterosexual bedrooms.
Okay, well, guess I'm your new neighbor.
(Penny:)- Penny.
- Leonard. Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)- Hi.
- Hi.
(Sheldon:)Hi.
(Leonard:)Well...
(Leonard:)Oh, welcome to the building.
Oh, thank you.
Maybe we can have coffee sometime.